{
    "basic": [
        {
            "id": 1,
            "question": "How many times do Muslims pray daily?",
            "description": "This question is to check your level",
            "options": [
                "3",
                "4",
                "5",
                "6"
            ],
            "answer": 1
        },
        {
            "id": 2,
            "question": "What is your level?",
            "description": "This question will help you determine what is the best for you",
            "options": [
                "basic",
                "moderate",
                "advanced"
            ],
            "answer": 0
        },
        {
            "id": 3,
            "question": "What is the name of the tribe of our Holy Prophet?",
            "description": "Our Holy prophet's tribe is one of the most important",
            "options": [
                "Banu Aws",
                "Banu Umayyah",
                "Banu Makhzum",
                "Banu Quraysh"
            ],
            "answer": 3
        },
        {
            "id": 4,
            "question": "Which battle is considered the first major battle in Islamic history?",
            "description": "This is one of the most important battles in Islamic history",
            "options": [
                "Battle of Uhud",
                "Battle of Badr",
                "Battle of Khandaq",
                "Battle of Hunayn"
            ],
            "answer": 1
        }
    ],
    "moderate": [
        {
            "id": 1,
            "question": "Are you new Muslim?",
            "description": "This question is to know more about you",
            "options": [
                "yes",
                "no"
            ],
            "answer": 1
        },
        {
            "id": 2,
            "question": "What is your level?",
            "description": "This question will help you determine what is the best for you",
            "options": [
                "basic",
                "moderate",
                "advanced"
            ],
            "answer": 0
        },
        {
            "id": 3,
            "question": "What is the name of the tribe of our Holy Prophet?",
            "description": "Our Holy prophet's tribe is one of the most important",
            "options": [
                "Banu Aws",
                "Banu Umayyah",
                "Banu Makhzum",
                "Banu Quraysh"
            ],
            "answer": 3
        },
        {
            "id": 4,
            "question": "Which battle is considered the first major battle in Islamic history?",
            "description": "This is one of the most important battles in Islamic history",
            "options": [
                "Battle of Uhud",
                "Battle of Badr",
                "Battle of Khandaq",
                "Battle of Hunayn"
            ],
            "answer": 1
        }
    ],
    "advanced": [
        {
            "id": 1,
            "question": "Are you new Muslim?",
            "description": "This question is to know more about you",
            "options": [
                "yes",
                "no"
            ],
            "answer": 1
        },
        {
            "id": 2,
            "question": "What is your level?",
            "description": "This question will help you determine what is the best for you",
            "options": [
                "basic",
                "moderate",
                "advanced"
            ],
            "answer": 0
        },
        {
            "id": 3,
            "question": "What is the name of the tribe of our Holy Prophet?",
            "description": "Our Holy prophet's tribe is one of the most important",
            "options": [
                "Banu Aws",
                "Banu Umayyah",
                "Banu Makhzum",
                "Banu Quraysh"
            ],
            "answer": 3
        },
        {
            "id": 4,
            "question": "Which battle is considered the first major battle in Islamic history?",
            "description": "This is one of the most important battles in Islamic history",
            "options": [
                "Battle of Uhud",
                "Battle of Badr",
                "Battle of Khandaq",
                "Battle of Hunayn"
            ],
            "answer": 1
        }
    ]
}